<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>netsplit</title><link>https://netsplit.uk/</link><description>Recent content on netsplit</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:22:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://netsplit.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to build a remote Proxmox and pfSense lab on an OVH dedicated server</title><link>https://netsplit.uk/posts/2022/10/19/remote_ovh_lab/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:22:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://netsplit.uk/posts/2022/10/19/remote_ovh_lab/</guid><description>Introduction This guide details how to set up a remote lab with a pfSense gateway on an OVH dedicated server, including basic firewall rules for managing access to the router&amp;rsquo;s web interface, and use of Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt for SSL certificates.
It was previously split into four parts which were written in 2019, but has now been consolidated into one post for readability and updated to still be valid in 2022 after OVH merged SoYouStart into its main control panel.</description></item><item><title>How to build a Mattermost Chatbot in Perl</title><link>https://netsplit.uk/posts/2019/01/09/mattermost-bot/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 17:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://netsplit.uk/posts/2019/01/09/mattermost-bot/</guid><description>Introduction WebService::Mattermost is an alternative Mattermost chatbot library written in Perl. It provides two interfaces to the Mattermost API and WebSocket gateway: from a script, and as a base for Moo and Moose classes. In this article, I will cover how to use it in a basic script, and demonstrate with a bot which greets users.
Requirements Installable from CPAN:
WebService::Mattermost (source) Final code For anyone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to read, here is the final product.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://netsplit.uk/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://netsplit.uk/about/</guid><description>Content Posts on this website are written by Mike Jones and it serves as a dumping ground for how-to guides I&amp;rsquo;ve written which are probably only useful to me.
Please feel free to submit content corrections by raising an issue or opening a pull request on the website&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repository.
Technology This website is built with Hugo, HTML5 and is JavaScript-free. Its source can be found on GitHub. Its design is kept simple on purpose in an attempt to follow principles set out by &amp;ldquo;Better Motherfucking Website&amp;rdquo;, and earlier &amp;ldquo;Motherfucking Website&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>